Gotta Be Somebody
歌手:Shayne Ward
压制：随Feng
This time I wonder what it feels like
这次 我想知道那是什麼感觉
To find the one in this life
为了找到这一生
The one we all dream of
我们追求的那一个人
But dreams just aren't enough
但只是幻想是不够的
So I'll be waiting for the real thing.
让我能够认出那个人
I'll know it by the feeling.
等待它成真
The moment when we're meeting
当我们相遇时
Will play out like a scene straight off the silver screen
会像电影情节一般从荧幕上退去
So I'll be holdin' my own breath
所以我会摒住呼吸
Right up to the end
直到结束
Until that moment when
直到那一刻
I find the one that I'll spend forever with
我终於找到那追求已久的人
'Cause nobody wants to be the last one there.
人们都渴望不被遗忘
'Cause everyone wants to feel like someone cares.
人们都希望被珍惜
Someone to love with my life in their hands.
一定有那个人重视我跟我们的爱
There's gotta be somebody for me like that.
一定有那样一个人为了我而存在
'Cause nobody wants to do it on their own
人们都渴望有个人可以分担生活
And everyone wants to know they're not alone.
人们都希望不再寂寞
There's somebody else that feels the same somewhere.
一定有个人跟我一样感同身受
There's gotta be somebody for me out there.
一定有那样一个人为了我而存在
Tonight, out on the street out in the moonlight
今晚 就在月光照耀的街道上
And dammit this feels too right
承认这感觉很美好吧
It's just like Déj? Vu
这场景仿佛似曾相识
Me standin' here with you
在你身边的我
So I'll be holdin`my own breath
我屏息以待
Could this be the end?
能让世界在这美好的一刻结束吗
Is it that moment when
这就是那一刻吗
I find the one that I'll spend forever with?
我终於找到那追求已久的人
'Cause nobody wants to be the last one there
人们都渴望不被遗忘
'Cause everyone wants to feel like someone cares.
人们都希望被珍惜
Someone to love with my life in their hands.
一定有那个人重视我跟我们的爱
There's gotta be somebody for me like that.
一定有那样一个人 为了我而存在
'Cause nobody wants to do it on their own
人们都渴望有个人可以分担生活
And everyone wants to know they're not alone.
人们都希望不再寂寞
There's somebody else that feels the same somewhere
一定有个人跟我一样感同身受
There's gotta be somebody for me out there.
一定有那样一个人 为了我而存在
'Cause nobody wants to be the last one there.
人们都渴望不被遗忘
And everyone wants to feel like someone cares.
人们都希望被珍惜
Someone to love with my life in their hands.
一定有那个人重视我跟我们的爱情
There has gotta be somebody for me
一定有那样一个人为了我而存在
Ohhhhhh.
'Cause nobody wants to be the last one there
人们都渴望不被遗忘
'Cause everyone wants to feel like someone cares.
人们都希望被珍惜
Someone to love with my life in their hands.
一定有那个人重视我跟我们的爱情
There's gotta be somebody for me like that.
一定有那样一个人 为了我而存在
Nobody wants to do it on their own
人们都渴望有有个人可以分担生活
And everyone wants to know they're not alone.
人们都希望不再寂寞
Is there somebody else that feels the same somewhere?
有人跟我一样的感受吗
There's gotta be somebody for me out there.
一定有那样一个人为了我而存在
压制：随Feng